# WYATT REVALEE

Terre Haute, Indiana · (618) 553-0037

Wyatt.revalee@gmail.com / wrevalee@sycamores.indstate.edu · wyatt-revalee.netlify.app

# SKILLS / CODING EXPERIENCE

**JUNE 2022 - PRESENT** 

# **VIDEOGAME DEVELOPMENT** UNITY ENGINE – C#

In the summer of 2022, I started developing my own game with Unity Engine.

It applies a lot of my knowledge I've obtained from school over my four years, as well as pushed me to learn another language (C#). Code and demo are available on my website and GitHub.

**AUGUST 2018 - PRESENT** 

# **SCHOOL CODING WORK INDIANA STATE UNIVERSITY**

There have been a lot of assignments that I have worked on over the years, ranging from simple to rather complex. Some of this code I have uploaded to GitHub to be seen.

# **EDUCATION**

**MAY 2018** 

# HIGH SCHOOL DIPLOMA, HUTSONVILLE HIGHSCHOOL

3.5 GPA, Officer of National Honor Society.

**CURRENT – GRADUATION IN MAY 2023** 

# **BACHELOR'S DEGREE OF COMPUTER SCIENCE, INDIANA STATE UNIVERSITY**

Currently a 2<sup>nd</sup> semester senior, graduating in the spring. 2.8 GPA.

# **SKILLS**

- Python, JavaScript, C, C#
- Lots of teamworking experience

- Communication
- Problem Solving

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# **JULY 2022 – DECEMBER 2022**

# **PRINT & MARKETING TECH, STAPLES TERRE HAUTE**

Many responsibilities, such as greeting customers and addressing their needs, creating and working on job tickets, maintaining the print and marketing area of the store (working with machines, ordering supplies, addressing issues, etc.), and working as a team.

#### **JULY 2020 – JANUARY 2022**

# TAKEAWAY SERVER, OUTBACK STEAKHOUSE

Responsible for taking and completing orders for takeout, as well as managing the takeout team.

#### SEPTEMBER 2018 – FEBRUARY 2020

# **COMPUTER TECHNICIAN, INDIANA STATE UNIVERSITY, TECH SUPPORT CENTER**

Working with software and hardware teams to create tickets, solve software issues for customers, and setting up new devices for students and faculty. As well as working front desk to address customer issues up front and assign them to a proper team to be worked on.